const data = [
  {
    question: "Who is the most Ballon D'or titles winner ?",
    choices: ["Ronaldo", "Messi", "Pele", "Maradona"],
    answer: "Messi",
  },
  {
    question: "Who scored in 2014 world cup final ?",
    choices: ["Messi", "Hummels", "Di Maria", "Gotze"],
    answer: "Gotze",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is France 2018 captain ?",
    choices: ["Pogba", "Benzema", "Kante", "Lloris"],
    answer: "Lloris",
  },
  {
    question: "Who did win 1998 world cup title?",
    choices: ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "France"],
    answer: "France",
  },
  {
    question: "Who had the invincibles team ?",
    choices: ["Man United", "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea"],
    answer: "Arsenal",
  },
  {
    question: "What's Shevichenko nationality ?",
    choices: ["Poland", "Ukraine", "Germany", "Serbia"],
    answer: "Ukraine",
  },
  {
    question: "What's Ibra nationality?",
    choices: ["Spain", "Italy", "Scotland", "Sweden"],
    answer: "Sweden",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is world cup top scorer ?",
    choices: ["Pele", "Maradona", "Cristiano", "Klose"],
    answer: "Klose",
  },
  {
    question: "Who did win 2007 Ballon D'or?",
    choices: ["Ronaldo", "Messi", "Ronaldinho", "Kaka"],
    answer: "Kaka",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is top titled player in history ?",
    choices: ["Messi", "Ronaldo", "Alves", "Ramos"],
    answer: "Alves",
  },
]

export default data
